Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Marie Rose Krikorian Series (Box 5, Box 9, Box 1)
  - An individual portrait of a man in front of a boat., Circa 1960-1980; ref1167; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Men; Boats/Ships; Ports; Mountains/Hills; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Lucerne, Switzerland; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a man reading., Circa 1960-1980; ref1168; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Men; Books; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Buildings; Lucerne, Switzerland; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a man in the woods., Circa 1960-1980; ref1169; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Syria; Interlaken, Switzerland; Forest/Woodlands; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A street in Interlaken, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1170; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Cars/Trucks; Interlaken, Switzerland; Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Landscaping at Rietberg Museum in Zurich, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1171; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Landscapes; Museums; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Zurich, Switzerland
  - An individual portrait of a man sitting on a bench in front of a statue., Circa 1960-1980; ref1172; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Men; Statues/Sculptures; Water; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Zurich, Switzerland; Syria; French Writing
  - A lake near a mountain in Lucerne, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1173; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Water; Mountains/Hills; Boats/Ships; Landscapes; Lucerne, Switzerland; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing
  - A cathedral in Lucerne, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1174; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Churches; Lucerne, Switzerland; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A building in Interlaken, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1175; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Buildings; Streets/Roads; Interlaken, Switzerland; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - St. Peter's Church in Zurich, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1176; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 9)
    St. Peter's Church of Zurich; Zurich, Switzerland; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a man in front of a body of water., Circa 1960-1980; ref1177; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Water; Mountains/Hills; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Lucerne, Switzerland
  - A fountain in Zurich, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1178; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Statues/Sculptures; Fountains; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Parks; Zurich, Switzerland; Syria
  - A landscape of Lucerne, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1179; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Landscapes; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Lucerne, Switzerland; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A forest in Interlaken, Switzerland., Circa 1960-1980; ref1180; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Forest/Woodlands; Landscapes; Interlaken, Switzerland; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a person wearing a patterned shirt., Circa 1960-1980; ref1181; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Syria
  - An individual portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian's eyes., Circa 1950-1965; ref1182; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8 x 6 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - A group portrait of several children standing in a field., Circa 1960-1980; ref1183; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.1 x 8.6 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Girls; Boys; Children; Cars/Trucks; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several men and women., Circa 1960-1980; ref1184; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 6.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of two women, one is smoking (linked ref1186)., Circa 1960-1980; ref1185; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Women; Smoking; Cigarettes; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group picture of a man and woman sitting at a table outside (linked ref1185)., Circa 1960-1980; ref1186; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - An individual portrait of Jareh Krikorian., Circa 1940-1965; ref1187; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian wearing a hat (linked ref1189,1190)., Circa 1940-1965; ref1188; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - An individual portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian wearing a hat (linked ref1188,1190)., Circa 1940-1965; ref1189; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - An individual portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian wearing a hat (linked ref1188,1189)., Circa 1940-1965; ref1190; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Hats; Women; Syria
  - A studio envelope from Photo Cine., Circa 1960-1980; ref1191; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 10 cm (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Syria
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian and another man., Circa 1950-1970; ref1193; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Men; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of several men and women under an archway., Circa 1960-1975; ref1194; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of a woman and three children at a swimming pool., Circa 1960-1975; ref1195; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Swimming Pools; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait with Marie Rose Krikorian, two men, two women, and three children., Circa 1960-1975; ref1196; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Men; Women; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian sitting with two men at a table., Circa 1950-1970; ref1197; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Women; Men; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Restaurants/bars
  - An individual portrait of a woman sitting on a bench., Circa 1950-1970; ref1198; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Women; Parks; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; French Writing
  - A group portrait of a woman talking to a man, another man is in the background., Circa 1950-1970; ref1199; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Men; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and a child., Circa 1950-1970; ref1200; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Women; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian walking., Circa 1950-1970; ref1201; Studio Elias Hichme, Bab Tuma, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.1 x 6.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Women; Men; Group Portraits; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of people eating near a mountain, including Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian., Circa 1950-1970; ref1202; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 7 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Mountains/Hills; Men; Women; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian with a man and a woman, taken in front of a mountain., May 3 1962; ref1203; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.7 x 8.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Mountains/Hills; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian with a man in front of a waterfall., Circa 1950-1960; ref1204; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Waterfalls; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian standing with a man and a woman in front of a body of water., Circa 1950-1960; ref1205; Photo Storm, Hildesheim, Germany; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Cars/Trucks; Water; Mountains/Hills; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of Jareh and Marie Rose Krikorian with their children in front of a statue of Mary., Circa 1950-1970; ref1206; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.7 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Statues/Sculptures
  - A group portrait of two children in a swimming pool., Circa 1950-1960; ref1207; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Boys; Swimming; Swimming Pools; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian with several adults and children., Circa 1950-1960; ref1208; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 5.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Boys; Children; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian., Circa 1950-1960; ref1209; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 x 3.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Women; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A group portrait with Marie Rose Krikorian at her son's baptism., Circa 1950-1960; ref1210; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Men; Women; Children; Baptisms; Religion; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A greeting card from the Argentinian embassy., Circa 1950-1970; ref1211; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.8 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Syria; French Writing; Embassies
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian, another man, and two women at a table., Circa 1950-1970; ref1212; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a woman holding a baby., Circa 1950-1970; ref1213; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 5.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Children; Women; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian dressed in costumes., 1954; ref1214; Studio Elias Hichme, Bab Tuma, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.7 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Women; Costumes; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - An individual portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian wearing a costume., 1954; ref1215; Studio Elias Hichme, Bab Tuma, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.7 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Women; Costumes
  - A group portrait of several boys., 1955; ref1216; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.1 x 6.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Boys; Children; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of several adults, including Marie Rose Krikorian, having a picnic., Circa 1950-1970; ref1217; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Men; Women; Picnic; Gatherings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Food
  - An individual portrait of a woman using a PFAFF Sewing Machine., Circa 1950-1960; ref1218; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 13 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Women; Machines; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Sewing; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian sitting with two men and a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1219; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Men; Women; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - An envelope with "Coiffure Michel" on it., Circa 1950-1970; ref1220; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 20.6 x 14 cm (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Damascus, Syria; Women; Jewelry; Arabic Calligraphy
  - An individual portrait of a child reaching for something., Circa 1945-1960; ref1221; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of Jareh and Marie Rose Krikorian with another woman (linked ref1223)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1222; Studio Liban, Beirut, Lebanon; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Buildings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Beirut, Lebanon; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of Jareh and Marie Rose Krikorian with another woman in a restaurant (linked ref1222)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1223; Studio Liban, Beirut, Lebanon; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Men; Women; Restaurants/bars; Syria; Beirut, Lebanon; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several adults, including Marie Rose Krikorian, laying with each other., Circa 1950-1960; ref1224; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Women; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Picnic; Gatherings
  - A group portrait of seven boys., Circa 1945-1960; ref1225; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Boys; Children; Mountains/Hills; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a baby in a bath and a girl., Circa 1950-1960; ref1226; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Girls; Children; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of two women in Fontainebleau, France., April, 1950; ref1227; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Fontainebleau, France; Buildings; Women; Group Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; French Writing
  - A group portrait of several men and women on a bench., Circa 1950-1970; ref1228; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.1 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Men; Women; Parks; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and two of her children (linked ref1230, 1240)., Circa 1945-1960; ref1229; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Women; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and two of her children (linked ref1229, 1240)., Circa 1945-1960; ref1230; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Women; Syria; Photographic Prints; Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a man next two a statue of two men., Circa 1960-1980; ref1231; Photo Cine, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 9 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Syria; Lucerne, Switzerland; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Buildings; Water
  - An individual portrait of a man in front of a body of water., Circa 1960-1980; ref1232; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Buildings; Water; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a boy and two other children in the background., Circa 1945-1960; ref1233; Studio Elias Hichme, Bab Tuma, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Boys; Fur Garments; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Damascus, Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A city., Circa 1950-1970; ref1234; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Buildings; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of four boys., Circa 1945-1960; ref1235; Studio Elias Hichme, Bab Tuma, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Damascus, Syria; Boys; Uniforms; Fur Garments; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian with their son and another man., 1955; ref1236; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.1 x 6.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Men; Women; Religion; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a boy., Circa 1945-1960; ref1237; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Children; Boys; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a baby., Circa 1945-1960; ref1238; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.1 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian and one of his sons., 20 August 1959; ref1239; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Men; Boys; Buildings; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and two of her children (linked ref1229, 1230)., Circa 1945-1960; ref1240; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6 cm (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - A group portrait of a woman next to a baby in a stroller., Circa 1950-1970; ref1241; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Women; Prams/Buggies/Strollers; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of a boy and two girls., Circa 1945-1960; ref1242; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.7 x 7.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Boys; Girls; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of five women, including Marie Rose Krikorian, and a man., Circa 1945-1960; ref1243; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - A building., Circa 1960-1980; ref1244; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Buildings; Landscapes; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian and a man and woman in front of a body of water (linked ref1246, 1247)., Circa 1970-1980; ref1245; Photo Storm, Hildesheim, Germany; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Hildesheim, Germany; Syria; Men; Women; Water; Mountains/Hills; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks
  - A group portrait of Jareh Krikorian and two men (linked ref1245, 1247)., Circa 1970-1980; ref1246; Photo Storm, Hildesheim, Germany; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Hildesheim, Germany; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Water; Mountains/Hills; Cars/Trucks
  - A group portrait of two men and a woman (linked ref1245, 1246)., Circa 1970-1980; ref1247; Photo Storm, Hildesheim, Germany; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Hildesheim, Germany; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Water; Mountains/Hills; Cars/Trucks
  - A city., Circa 1960-1980; ref1248; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Buildings; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Syria
  - A group portrait of two boys., Circa 1945-1960; ref1249; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.3 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian reading next to their two sons., Circa 1945-1970; ref1250; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Boys; Children; Men; Women; Newspapers/Magazines; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a man overlooking water., Circa 1960-1980; ref1251; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Water; Boats/Ships
  - An individual portrait of a man in front of a body of water., Circa 1960-1980; ref1252; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Mountains/Hills; Syria
  - A desk., Circa 1960-1980; ref1253; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 8.7 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Furnishings; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A table., Circa 1960-1980; ref1254; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose and Jareh Krikorian in Nice., November 1948; ref1255; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.9 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Nice, France; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Group Portraits; Syria; Women; Men
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian and a man wearing kimonos., Circa 1970-1980; ref1256; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - An individual portrait of Jareh Krikorian reading a newspaper., Circa 1950-1965; ref1257; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Men; Newspapers/Magazines; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man kissing a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1258; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.4 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Men; Women; Children; Cigarettes; Smoking; Kissing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of Marie Rose Krikorian with another woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1259; Studio Liban, Beirut, Lebanon; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Beirut, Lebanon; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bags/Purses; Group Portraits; Women